Police Chief!
They said they're from the Provincial Bureau's Inspection Division.
They forced their way in.
I couldn't stop them.
Mu Gui.
Under Director Wu's orders, we're taking
you back for suspension and investigation.
Something's wrong.
Move!
Move! Take him away! Mu Ying!
Something's wrong!
Boss.
We're done searching.
Nothing suspicious.
You two, go check over there again.
Yes, sir.
Be thorough. Yes, sir.
Inspector Mu.
No, wait.
Police Chief.
Lijia Town's officers follow your orders.
We'll go through fire and water
without hesitation.
Please be the bigger person
and forgive us for not following orders before.
Shut up.
Cut the crap.
Keep accurate investigation records.
Yes, right away.
Judging from the marks on the bones,
they died from drowning.
Before they died,
there were signs of struggle.
Using the human foundation sacrifice
as an excuse, Benefactor Li drowned them.
How ruthless and wicked.
Unforgivable.
But
Benefactor Li did build bridges and roads.
He did a lot of good deeds.
You're wrong.
Benefactor Li didn't build them
to benefit the people at all.
He just wanted to win people's hearts
and pose as a great benefactor
to cover up stealing tomb artifacts
and committing murder.
The gold shop he opened in town
wasn't to boost the local economy either.
It was to turn the gold from the tombs
into jewelry and sell it.
Your town
was his best money-making tool.
To Lijia Town,
the great benefactor they revered
was actually
a heinous tomb raider
and murderer.
Burrowing Rat,
Elder Ding,
Xiaobao,
We can finally say
we've avenged you.
I hope you can rest in peace now.
We'd better
properly bury the grandpa and grandson.
You have been avenged.
You may rest in peace now.
Master.
You're hallucinating again.
Jiang Huai,
in a few days,
I'll take you to the provincial hospital
to see what's really wrong with your eyes.
Sure.
There's one thing I still don't get.
Can you tell me now
why you helped me?
Helping you investigate the case...
...was actually for my own selfish reasons.
I've been trying to recover
the ancient book stolen from our library,
Heavenly Craftsmanship.
So, did you find it?
At the Li Manor,
I only saw the box it was kept in,
but the book wasn't inside.
In this entire world,
there's only one Heavenly Craftsmanship.
So I have to get it back.
All right.
Since you helped me solve the case,
I'll help you track down the ancient book.
Okay.
Thank you.
Kid.
I've saved your master so many times.
You said
you'd work like a dog for me.
What are you doing?
Let's go.
Wait.
Do you need something?
I do.
What do you want?
That she-devil.
And she has the nerve to say
she's the top student from the academy.
Look at this mess.
How can anyone live here?
Bossing me around.
Useless at everything else,
but number one at being a pig.
Watch how I deal with her.
Xun.
Don't blame me for not warning you.
Are you sure you can take a beating?
It's fine.
Watch me scare her to death.
Shaman.
You took Benefactor Li's money
to practice superstitious nonsense
and indirectly helped Benefactor Li
kill Elder Ding and Xiaobao.
As you didn't commit the crime directly,
the Police Chief granted special permission.
You can go now.
I was foolish
and made a mistake.
Thank you for your mercy, Police Chief.
Once you're out of here,
drop that superstitious act.
I will definitely turn over a new leaf
and live an honest life.
Master Li.
Take care.
I'll pray and burn incense for you daily.
These prayer beads will keep you safe.
Put them on.
Let's go.
Police Chief!
The shaman has been released.
Who did this?
Was it you, little brat?
You kid...
Is there something wrong with you?
I didn't do it.
You want evidence? If not you, who did it?
If not you, did he do it?
If that she-devil wasn't stopped earlier,
the washbasin would've hit her for sure.
By the same logic,
if Benefactor Li
hadn't been delayed by other things,
he'd be dead by now,
nor would the others be killed by mistake.
What's the deal with this kid?
Stop arguing!
In the Li manor case,
we missed another killer.
What?
Missed another killer?
That's right.
Hurry.
Bring Benefactor Li in for questioning!
Let's go.
Move!
You're absolutely right.
There is indeed such an expert.
He knows everything.
I have plans with my wife. I must leave.
Sir,
please go back for now.
I have a big deal
that I can only discuss with you.
What big deal?
That ancient book, Heavenly Craftsmanship,
is in your hands.
That's right.
This book is mine.
I bought it from out of town.
Sell this book to me.
Sir,
how much silver do you want?
Name your price.
But this book
is a unique Ming dynasty copy.
It's priceless.
I'm not selling.
Then what if we use your life
in exchange for this book?
I guarantee you won't die.
How about it?
This expert,
he kept his word.
He saved me from assassination every time,
causing Chunmei and the others
to kill Mengzhu and my wife by mistake.
What did this expert look like?
Every time he came to see me,
he wore a suit and...
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
Benefactor Li!
What's wrong?
Someone!
Get him to a hospital!
Someone, hurry!
Benefactor Li!